{
    "subject": "Mieszko_III_the_Old",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Eudoxia_of_Kiev",
    "human_readable": "Mieszko III the Old is married to Eudoxia of Kiev.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9886654615402222,
            "question": "Is Eudoxia of Kiev married to Mieszko III the Old?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9835829138755798,
            "question": "Who are the spouses in this relationship: Mieszko III the Old and Eudoxia of Kiev?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9509634971618652,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Mieszko III the Old and Eudoxia of Kiev?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9329344630241394,
            "question": "To whom was Mieszko III the Old married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9260817766189575,
            "question": "Who is Mieszko III the Old married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9258261322975159,
            "question": "Who is Eudoxia of Kiev married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9236569404602051,
            "question": "Eudoxia of Kiev is the wife of whom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.921302318572998,
            "question": "Name the wife of Mieszko III the Old."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.80794757604599,
            "question": "What is the name of Mieszko III the Old's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8077749609947205,
            "question": "What was the name of Mieszko III the Old's spouse?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mieszko III the Old is married to Eudoxia of Kiev.",
            "html": "yago_29332_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Mieszko III the Old's wife?",
            "html": "yago_29332_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the wife of Mieszko III the Old.",
            "html": "yago_29332_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eudoxia of Kiev is the wife of whom?",
            "html": "yago_29332_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29332_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29332_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29332_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29332_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29332_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29332_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29332_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29332_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29332_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29332_60.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the triple \"Mieszko III the Old is married to Eudoxia of Kiev\" is supported by the context information provided. The various documents mention Eudoxia as the wife of Mieszko III the Old, and they also provide details about their marriage and children."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Mieszko III the Old married Eudoxia of Kiev in 1154, and they had several children together. Therefore, the statement \"Mieszko III the Old is married to Eudoxia of Kiev\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}